Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
- Series 3: Architectural Drawings (Oversized), 1893-1993; 6 boxes; 212 folders
  - Firestone Library drawings, 1945 September 9-1948 October 10; 17 folders; 158 items
    - Openings in South Wall Reserve Reading Room Terrace, 1947 May 05; 335; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 208)
    - Details of Jambs and Mullions for Large Windows in Lounge 301, 1947 May 05; 336; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 208)
    - Plan Thru Center Pier and Interior Elevation of Large Windows in Lounge 301, 1947 May 05; 337; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 208)
    - Section Thru Limestone Sill for Large Windows in Lounge 301, 1947 May 05; 338; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 208)
    - Section Thru Arch and Interior Sill for Large Windows in Lounge 301, 1947 May 05; 339; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 208)
    - Sections "V"-"V" and "W"-"W" On Scale Drawing Number 120, 1947 May 05; 340; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 208)
    - F.S. Details of Ends of Granite Sills in Loggia, 1947 June 06; 341; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Lintel Over Door #170 Limestone Terrace Copings, 1947 May 05; 342; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Plan and Details of Turret on Southwest Corner of Tower, 1947 August 08; 343; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Section Thru Lower Part of Turret on Southwest Corner of Tower, 1947 August 08; 344; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Coping and Crenelation Northwest Bay, 1947 June 06; 345; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Terminus of Wall Reserve Reading Room, 1947 June 06; 346; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Detail of Limestone Gables at Intersection of Turrets and Wall on Upper Part of Tower, 1947 June 06; 347; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Details of Limestone Pinnacles at Parapet on CL of Tower Windows, 1947 July 07; 348; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
    - Detail of Lower Part of Weather Vane, 1947 August 08; 349; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 209)
  - Forrestal Campus Drawings, 1954; 1 box; 44 folders
    June 2000 Accession
    - Part of the Penn Accelerator Complex, undated; 1-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 1)
    - Part of the Plasma Physics Laboratory, undated; 1-B; 1 folder (Folder Not located)
    - Modifications and Additions to these Three Buildings, Especially Mechanical and Physical Plant Details, undated; 1-ABC; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 2)
    - Additions to the Meson Research Area of Plasma Physics Laboratory, undated; 1-B2; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 3)
    - Details for the Extension of an Electrical Substation, undated; 1-D; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 3)
    - Engineering and Administration Building, undated; 1-E; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 4)
    - Liquid Hydrogen Experiment Building, undated; 1-G; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 5)
    - PPA External Beam Facility, undated; 1-H; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 6)
    - Extension to PPA External Beam Facility, undated; 1-HA; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 7)
    - Additions and Alterations to an Office and Electrical Testing Facility, undated; 1-K; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 8)
    - Maintenance Building for Materials Handling Equipment, undated; 1-L; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 8)
    - Laboratories and Shops Building, undated; 1-N; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 8, Folder Oversize folder 9)
    - Addition of Sewer Facilities and Extension of Office Building, undated; 1-O; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 9)
    - Sewer Work of Sewer Facilities and New Office Facilities, undated; 1-P; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 9)
    - Sayre Hall, undated; 2-A; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 10, Folder 11)
    - New Auditorium, undated; 2-B; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 12)
    - Wind Tunnel, undated; 2-G; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 12)
    - Aero Laboratory, undated; 2-L; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 12)
    - Roof Framing Details, undated; 3C; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 12)
    - Rigid Building Frame Details, undated; 3-D; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 12)
    - Forward Flight Facility, undated; 3-DA; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 13)
    - Chemical Sciences Building, undated; 4-A; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 13, Folder 14)
    - Isotope Separator Building, undated; 4-B; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 15)
    - Gas Dynamics Laboratory, undated; 5; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 15)
    - Animal House and Laboratory, Department of Animal Pathology, undated; 5-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 15)
    - Connecting Wing Between Buildings C and D, undated; 5-B; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 15)
    - Gas Dynamics Lab, undated; 5-C; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 16)
    - Revision to Gas Dynamics Lab Concerning Helium Recovery System, undated; 5-D; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 16)
    - Gas Dynamics Building, undated; 5-F; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 17)
    - Machine Shop, undated; 6-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 17)
    - Operation and Autopsy Building, Isolation Building, undated; 6-B; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 18)
    - Stock Room, undated; 6-C; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 19)
    - Guggenheim Jet Propulsion Laboratory - Office Building, undated; 8-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 20)
    - Jet Propulsion Research - Lab Building, undated; 8-B; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 20)
    - Jet Propulsion Research - Lab Building, undated; 8-C; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 21)
    - Jet Propulsion Research Assemly Shop (Formerly Compressor Building), undated; 8-D; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 21)
    - Jet Propulsion Research Storage Building (Formerly Animal Pathology Feed House), undated; 8-E; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 21)
    - Solid Propellant Processing Building, undated; 8-G; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 26)
    - Solid Propellant Storage Shed, undated; 8-H; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 26)
    - Guggenheim Laboratory Building, undated; 8-I; 5 folders (Folder Oversize folder 25, Folder Oversize folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29)
    - Boiler House and Cafeteria, undated; 9-A; 4 folders (Folder Oversize folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder Oversize folder 25)
    - Well House Number Seven, undated; 9-E; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 30)
    - Project Matterhorn Building One, undated; 10-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 30)
    - Project Matterhorn Site Plan, undated; 10-B; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 30)
    - Project Matterhorn Revisions to Building Two, undated; 10-C; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 30)
    - Project Matterhorn New Electrical Installations, All Buildings, undated; 10-CDE; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 31)
    - Project Matterhorn New Building, 1954; 10-G; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 31)
    - Flight Research Laboratory, undated; 11-B; 3 folders (Folder Oversize folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33)
    - Project Matterhorn - Gilson House, undated; 12-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 35)
    - Princeton University Auxiliary Library (Forrestal Annex), undated; 12-B; 3 folders (Folder Oversize folder 34, Folder Oversize folder 35, Folder Oversize folder 36)
    - Kennels and Barn, undated; 13-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 36)
    - Entrance Control Booth, undated; 13-F; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 36)
    - Geophysical Fluid Dynamics Laboratory (1 through 89), undated; 18-A; 5 folders (Folder Oversize folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40, Folder 41)
    - Geophysical Fluid Dynamics Laboratory (90 through 148), undated; 18-A; 3 folders (Folder Oversize folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44)
    - Forrestal Campus Site Plans, dates not examined; 1 folder
      - Survey, undated; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 45, Folder 46)
      - Site and Master Plans, undated; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 47, Folder 48)
      - Airfield, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 49)
      - Roads and Plot Plans, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 50)
    - Forrestal Campus Utilities, dates not examined; 1 folder
      - Wells and Water, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 51)
      - Electrical, undated; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 52, Folder 53)
      - Tunnels, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 54)
      - Sewers, undated; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 55, Folder 56)
    - Forrestal Campus C Site, dates not examined; 1 folder
      - Phase 1-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 57)
      - Cafeteria Building, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 58)
      - Site COB Building, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 58)
      - General, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 58)
      - Maintenance Building, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 59)
      - New Shop Building, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 59)
      - Steam Plant, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 59)
      - PPL, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 59)
      - Warehouse, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 59)
      - Negatives (Uncatalogued), undated; 3 folders (Folder Oversize folder 60, Folder 61, Folder 62)
    - Tokamak Fusion Test Reactor, dates not examined; 1 box; 1 folder
      - Technical Shop Addition, undated; 1 box (Folder Oversize folder 64, Box 102)
      - Experimental Complex, undated; 1 box (Box 102)
      - Office and Laboratory Building, undated; 1 box (Box 102)
      - Progress Prints, undated; 1 box (Box 102)
      - Sitework, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 63)
    - Forrestal Campus Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder
      - FM (Miscellaneous Projects, Including Landscaping), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 65)
      - Forrestal Memorial, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 66)
      - Building Space (Survey of Occupied Office Spaces), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 66)
      - Forrestal Center (Landscaping Project), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 66)
      - Forrestal Village (Final Site Plan), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 66)
      - Director's House (Alterations to the Theobald Smith House), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 66)
      - Forrestal Research Center (Master Plan and Progress Prints for Various Buildings), undated; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 67, Folder 68)
    - Forrestal Rental Houses (Note: All 'B' Buildings are Outlying Structures [Garages, Barns, etc.]), dates not examined; 1 folder
      - House 9, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - Boarding House, undated; 214-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - 151-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - 148-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - 149-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - Robison House, undated; 150-A; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - 152-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - 153-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - 153-B, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 69)
      - 154-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 70)
      - 154-B, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 70)
      - 155-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 70)
      - 156-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 70)
      - 156-B, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 70)
      - 157-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 70)
      - 158-A, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 70)
  - "Black Book C" (Floor Plans), dates not examined; 3 folders
    - 1922 Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 1937 Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 1938 Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 1939 Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 1940 Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 1941 Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Aaron Burr Hall (First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Aaron Burr Hall (First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 106 Alexander (Ground, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 99 Alexander Street (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 120 Alexander Street (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 529 Alexander Road (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Baker Rink (Balcony), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Blair Hall (Tower, Fourth Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Boathouse (First, Second, Tower), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Boiler House (First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 171 Broadmead (Second Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Brown Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Caldes Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Chapel (Crypt), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Charlton Street 6-8 (Basement, First, Second, Attic), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 1927-Clapp Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third, Mezzanine), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Clio Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Cuyler Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 2 Dickinson Street (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 11 Dickinson Street (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 15 Dickinson Street (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 16 Dickinson Street (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - 24 Dickinson Street (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Dillon Gym (D Level), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Dinky Station North (Basement, First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Dinky Station South (Basement, First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Dod Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 71)
    - Dodge-Osborn Hall (Basement, Ground, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Edwards Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - 27 Edwards Place (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - 29 Edwards Place (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Elementary Particles Lab East (First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Elm Drive Substation (First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Eno Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Feinberg Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Mezzanine), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Fine Hall (Basement, A, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth, Sixth, Seventh, Eighth, Ninth, Tenth, Eleventh, Twelfth, Professor's Plan, Penthouse, Fan Room), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Fitzrandolph Observatory (Basement, First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Forbes College Addition (Basement), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Forrestal House Number Eight (First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Gauss Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Hamilton Hall (Ground, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Hoyt Chemical Laboratory (Basement, Ground, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - 17 Ivy Lane (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Jadwin Hall (Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Joline Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Jones Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Joseph Henry House (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Lenz Tennis Center (First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Lourie-Love Hall (Fourth Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Maclean House (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Marx Hall (Basement, First, Second, third, Penthouse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - McCarter Theater (Projection Booth, Tower Levels Three, Four, Five, Six), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Mudd Library (Basement, First, SEcond, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - 201 Nassau Street (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - 221 Nassau Street (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - New South (B, A, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth, Sixth, Seventh, Penthouse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Notestein Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 72)
    - Palmer House (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Patton Hall (Fourth Floor, Tower Plans Four and Five), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - 116 Prospect (Basement, First, Second, Attic), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Prospect House (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Rock Magnetism Lab (Ground Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Rowing Tank (Ground Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Sayre Hall (First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Stanhope Hall (Ground, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Stevenson 83 Prospect (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Stevenson 91 Prospect (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Third World Center (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - 35 University Place (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - 45 University Place (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - 48 University Place (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - 71 University Place (First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - 130 University Place (First Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Walker Hall (Ground, Third Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Washington House (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - 281 Washington Road (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - West College (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Whig Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third, Fourth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Wilcox Hall (Basement, First, Second), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Witherspoon Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Wu Hall (Basement, Main, First, Second, Mezzanine), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
    - Wyman House (Basement, First, Second, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 73)
  - Floor Plans, dates not examined; 1 folder
    - 185 Nassau Street (Basement, First, Second, Third Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 74)
    - 1903 Hall (Ground, First, Second, Third, Fourth Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 74)
    - 1915 Hall (Basement, First, Second Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 74)
  - "Black Book E" (Floor Plans), dates not examined; 1 folder
    - Architecture Building (First, Second, Balcony Level), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Baker Rink (Basement, First Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Patton Hall (Basement, Third Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Von Neuman Hall (Basement, First, Second Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Green Hall (Second, Third Floors), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Jadwin Gym (E, D, C, B, Main, Mezzanine, Upper Office, Grandstand), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Blair Hall (Third Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Holder Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Fourth, Fifth), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Thomas Laboratory (Ground, First, Second, Third, Greenhouse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Firestone Library (First, Second, Third, A, B, C Floors, Penthouse, Towers), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Little Hall (Basement, First, Second, Third, Tower), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Fischer/Corwin Bendheim (Basement, Ground, First, Second, Third, Penthouse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Forbes Main Building (Third Floor), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Frick Chem Lab (Basement, Ground, Third), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
    - Denunzio Pool (Mechanical, Deck, Concourse), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 77)
  - OPP and ENG Only (Survey Plans), dates not examined; 4 folders
    - Princeton University Campus Map (Control Points), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - Campus Maps (Index), undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - B-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - B-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - B-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - B-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - B-7, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - B-8, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - B-9, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-2, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-7, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-8, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-9, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - C-10, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - D-1, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - D-2, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - D-3, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 78)
    - D-4, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - D-5, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - D-6, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - D-7, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - D-8, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)
    - D-9, undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 79)